<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. -->
    <string name="app_name">Visit Venice</string>

    <!-- CATEGORY NAMES -->

    <!-- Name for the welcome category - landing category. -->
    <string name="category_welcome">Welcome to Venice</string>

    <!-- Name for sights category -->
    <string name="category_sights">Venice Top Sights</string>

    <!-- Name for hotels category -->
    <string name="category_hotels">Venice Hotels</string>

    <!-- Name for restaurants category -->
    <string name="category_restaurants">Venice Restaurants</string>

    <!-- Name for attractions category -->
    <string name="category_attractions">Venice Attractions</string>

    <!-- PLACEHOLDER STRINGS FOR ADAPTER INTENTS -->
    <string name="name_placeholder">name</string>
    <string name="address_placeholder">address</string>
    <string name="image_id_placeholder">image</string>
    <string name="description_placeholder">description</string>
    <string name="url_placeholder">url</string>

    <!-- IMAGE DESCRIPTIONS -->
    <string name="welcome_image_description">Photo of Venice.</string>
    <string name="place_image_description">Photo of the described place.</string>

    <!-- WELCOME CATEGORY -->

    <!-- Image labels -->
    <string name="welcome_image_label_1">Venice</string>
    <string name="welcome_image_label_2">Veneto, Italy</string>

    <!-- Main text -->
    <string name="welcome_text">Venice, the capital of northern Italy\'s Veneto region,
        is built on more than 100 small islands in a lagoon in the Adriatic Sea.
        It has no roads, just canals – including the Grand Canal thoroughfare –
        lined with Renaissance and Gothic palaces. The central square, Piazza San Marco,
        contains St. Mark\'s Basilica, which is tiled with Byzantine mosaics,
        and the Campanile bell tower offering views of the city’s red roofs.\n\n
        The Gothic pink-and-white-marble Doge\'s Palace sits on the east
        side of the piazza. Before the Christian holiday of Lent, this area becomes the epicenter
        of Venice\'s Carnival, where partygoers dress in elaborate masks and costumes.
        A gondola ride away are the Peggy Guggenheim Collection, an influential gallery
        of modern art, and the Galleria dell\'Accademia, a museum of Renaissance-era and Vedutisti
        paintings. The covered Rialto foot bridge leads to a market that supplies many of the
        city\'s fish-focused Venetian restaurants.</string>

    <!-- SIGHTS CATEGORY -->

    <string name="grand_canal_name">Grand Canal</string>
    <string name="grand_canal_address">30100 Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="grand_canal_description">The banks of the Grand Canal are lined with more than
        170 buildings, most of which date from the 13th to the 18th century, and demonstrate
        the welfare and art created by the Republic of Venice. The noble Venetian families faced
        huge expenses to show off their richness in suitable palazzos; this contest reveals
        the citizens\’ pride and the deep bond with the lagoon. Amongst the many are
        the Palazzi Barbaro, Ca\' Rezzonico, Ca\' d\'Oro, Palazzo Dario, Ca\' Foscari,
        Palazzo Barbarigo and to Palazzo Venier dei Leoni, housing the Peggy Guggenheim Collection.
        The churches along the canal include the basilica of Santa Maria della Salute.
        Centuries-old traditions, such as the Historical Regatta,
        are perpetuated every year along the Canal.\n\n
        Because most of the city\'s traffic goes along the Canal rather than across it, only one
        bridge crossed the canal until the 19th century, the Rialto Bridge. There are currently
        three more bridges, the Ponte degli Scalzi, the Ponte dell\'Accademia,
        and the controversial Ponte della Costituzione from 2008, designed by Santiago Calatrava,
        connecting the train station to Piazzale Roma, one of the few places in Venice where buses
        and cars can enter. As was usual in the past, people can still take a ferry ride across
        the canal at several points by standing up on the deck of a simple gondola called a
        traghetto, although this service is less common than even a decade ago.\n\n
        Most of the palaces emerge from water without pavement. Consequently,
        one can only tour past the fronts of the buildings on the grand canal by boat.</string>
    <string name="grand_canal_url">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Grand_Canal_(Venice)</string>
    <string name="st_marks_basilica_name">Saint Mark\'s Basilica</string>
    <string name="st_marks_basilica_address">Piazza San Marco, 328, 30100\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="st_marks_basilica_description">The Patriarchal Cathedral Basilica of Saint Mark
        (Italian: Basilica Cattedrale Patriarcale di San Marco), commonly known as Saint Mark\'s
        Basilica (Italian: Basilica di San Marco; Venetian: Baxéłega de San Marco),
        is the cathedral church of the Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Venice, northern Italy.
        It is the most famous of the city\'s churches and one of the best known examples
        of Italo-Byzantine architecture. It lies at the eastern end of the Piazza San Marco,
        adjacent and connected to the Doge\'s Palace. Originally it was the chapel of the Doge,
        and has only been the city\'s cathedral since 1807, when it became the seat of the
        Patriarch of Venice, archbishop of the Roman Catholic Archdiocese of Venice,
        formerly at San Pietro di Castello.\n\n
        For its opulent design, gold ground mosaics, and its status as a symbol of Venetian wealth
        and power, from the 11th century on the building has been known by the nickname
        Chiesa d\'Oro (Church of gold).</string>
    <string name="st_marks_basilica_url">http://www.basilicasanmarco.it/?lang=en</string>
    <string name="doges_palace_name">Doge\'s Palace</string>
    <string name="doges_palace_address">San Marco, 1, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="doges_palace_description">In 810, Doge Angelo Partecipazio moved the seat of
        government from the island of Malamocco to the area of the present-day Rialto, when it was
        decided a palatium duci, a ducal palace, should be built. However, no trace remains of that
        9th-century building as the palace was partially destroyed in the 10th century by a fire.
        The following reconstruction works were undertaken at the behest of Doge Sebastiano Ziani
        (1172–1178). A great reformer, he would drastically change the entire layout of the
        St. Mark\'s Square. The new palace was built out of fortresses, one façade to the Piazzetta,
        the other overlooking the St. Mark\'s Basin. Although only few traces remain of that palace,
        some Byzantine-Venetian architecture characteristics can still be seen at the ground floor,
        with the wall base in Istrian stone and some herring-bone pattern brick paving. Political
        changes in the mid-13th century led to the need to re-think the palace\'s structure due to
        the considerable increase in the number of the Great Council\'s members. The new Gothic
        palace\'s constructions started around 1340, focusing mostly on the side of the building
        facing the lagoon. Only in 1424, did Doge Francesco Foscari decide to extend the rebuilding
        works to the wing overlooking the Piazzetta, serving as law-courts, and with a ground floor
        arcade on the outside, open first floor loggias running along the façade, and the internal
        courtyard side of the wing, completed with the construction of the Porta della Carta (1442).
        \n\nIn 1483, a violent fire broke out in the side of the palace overlooking the canal, where
        the Doge\'s Apartments were. Once again, an important reconstruction became necessary and
        was commissioned from Antonio Rizzo, who would introduce the new Renaissance language to the
        building\'s architecture. An entire new structure was raised alongside the canal, stretching
        from the ponte della Canonica to the Ponte della Paglia, with the official rooms of the
        government decorated with works commissioned from Vittore Carpaccio, Giorgione,
        Alvise Vivarini and Giovanni Bellini. Another huge fire in 1547 destroyed some of the rooms
        on the second floor, but fortunately without undermining the structure as a whole.
        Refurbishment works were being held at the palace when on 1577 a third fire destroyed
        the Scrutinio Room and the Great Council Chamber, together with works by Gentile da Fabriano,
        Pisanello, Alvise Vivarini, Vittore Carpaccio, Giovanni Bellini, Pordenone, and Titian.
        In the subsequent rebuilding work it was decided to respect the original Gothic style,
        despite the submission of a neo-classical alternative designs by the influential Renaissance
        architect Andrea Palladio. However, there are some classical features — for example, since
        the 16th century, the palace has been linked to the prison by the Bridge of Sighs.
        As well as being the ducal residence, the palace housed political institutions of the
        Republic of Venice until the Napoleonic occupation of the city in 1797, when its role
        inevitably changed. Venice was subjected first to French rule, then to Austrian, and finally
        in 1866 it became part of Italy. Over this period, the palace was occupied by various
        administrative offices as well as housing the Biblioteca Marciana and other important
        cultural institutions within the city.\n\n
        By the end of the 19th century, the structure was showing clear signs of decay, and the
        Italian government set aside significant funds for its restoration and all public offices
        were moved elsewhere, with the exception of the State Office for the protection of historical
        Monuments, which is still housed at the palace\'s loggia floor. In 1923, the Italian State,
        owner of the building, entrusted the management to the Venetian municipality to be run as a
        museum. Since 1996, the Doge\’s Palace has been part of the Venetian museums network, which
        has been under the management of the Fondazione Musei Civici di Venezia since 2008.</string>
    <string name="doges_palace_url">http://palazzoducale.visitmuve.it/en/home/</string>
    <string name="piazza_san_marco_name">Piazza San Marco</string>
    <string name="piazza_san_marco_address">Piazza San Marco, 30100\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="piazza_san_marco_description">Piazza San Marco (Venetian: Piasa San Marco),
        often known in English as St Mark\'s Square, is the principal public square of Venice, Italy,
        where it is generally known just as la Piazza ("the Square"). All other urban spaces in the
        city (except the Piazzetta and the Piazzale Roma) are called campi ("fields"). The Piazzetta
        ("little Piazza/Square") is an extension of the Piazza towards the lagoon in its south east
        corner (see plan). The two spaces together form the social, religious and political centre
        of Venice and are commonly considered together.\n\n
        A remark usually attributed (though without proof) to Napoleon calls the Piazza San Marco
        "the drawing room of Europe".</string>
    <string name="piazza_san_marco_url">
        http://www.associazionepiazzasanmarco.it/it/visita-virtuale-piazza-san-marco.php</string>
    <string name="rialto_bridge_name">Rialto Bridge</string>
    <string name="rialto_bridge_address">Sestiere San Polo, 30125\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="rialto_bridge_description">The first dry crossing of the Grand Canal was a pontoon
        bridge built in 1181 by Nicolò Barattieri. It was called the Ponte della Moneta, presumably
        because of the mint that stood near its eastern entrance.\n\n
        The development and importance of the Rialto market on the eastern bank increased traffic on
        the floating bridge, so it was replaced in 1255 by a wooden bridge. This structure had two
        inclined ramps meeting at a movable central section, that could be raised to allow the
        passage of tall ships. The connection with the market eventually led to a change of name for
        the bridge. During the first half of the 15th century, two rows of shops were built along
        the sides of the bridge. The rents brought an income to the State Treasury, which helped
        maintain the bridge.\n\n
        Maintenance was vital for the timber bridge. It was partly burnt in the revolt led by
        Bajamonte Tiepolo in 1310. In 1444, it collapsed under the weight of a crowd watching a boat
        parade and it collapsed again in 1524.\n\n
        The idea of rebuilding the bridge in stone was first proposed in 1503. Several projects were
        considered over the following decades. In 1551, the authorities requested proposals for the
        renewal of the Rialto Bridge, among other things. Plans were offered by famous architects,
        such as Jacopo Sansovino, Palladio and Vignola, but all involved a Classical approach with
        several arches, which was judged inappropriate to the situation. Michelangelo also was
        considered as designer of the bridge.\n\n
        The present stone bridge, a single span designed by Antonio da Ponte, was finally completed
        in 1591. It is similar to the wooden bridge it succeeded. Two inclined ramps lead up to a
        central portico. On either side of the portico, the covered ramps carry rows of shops. The
        engineering of the bridge was considered so audacious that architect Vincenzo Scamozzi
        predicted future ruin. The bridge has defied its critics to become one of the architectural
        icons of Venice.\n\n
        Today, the Bridge is one of the top tourism attractions in Venice.</string>
    <string name="rialto_bridge_url">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Rialto_Bridge</string>
    <string name="gallerie_dell_accademia_name">Gallerie dell\'Accademia</string>
    <string name="gallerie_dell_accademia_address">Campo della Carita, 1050,
        30123\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="gallerie_dell_accademia_description">The Gallerie dell\'Accademia is a museum
        gallery of pre-19th-century art in Venice, northern Italy. It is housed in the Scuola della
        Carità on the south bank of the Grand Canal, within the sestiere of Dorsoduro. It was
        originally the gallery of the Accademia di Belle Arti di Venezia, the art academy of Venice,
        from which it became independent in 1879, and for which the Ponte dell\'Accademia and the
        Accademia boat landing station for the vaporetto water bus are named. The two institutions
        remained in the same building until 2004, when the art school moved to the Ospedale degli
        Incurabili.</string>
    <string name="gallerie_dell_accademia_url">http://www.gallerieaccademia.it/</string>
    <string name="st_marks_campanile_name">Saint Mark\'s Campanile</string>
    <string name="st_marks_campanile_address">Piazza San Marco, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="st_marks_campanile_description">St Mark\'s Campanile (Italian: Campanile di San
        Marco; Venetian: Canpanièl de San Marco) is the bell tower of St Mark\'s Basilica in Venice,
        Italy, located in the Piazza San Marco. It is one of the most recognizable symbols of the
        city.\n\nThe tower is 98.6 metres (323 ft) tall, and stands alone in a corner of St Mark\'s
        Square, near the front of the basilica. It has a simple form, the bulk of which is a fluted
        brick square shaft, 12 metres (39 ft) wide on each side and 50 metres (160 ft) tall, above
        which is a loggia surrounding the belfry, housing five bells. The belfry is topped by a cube,
        alternate faces of which show the Lion of St. Mark and the female representation of Venice
        (la Giustizia: Justice). The tower is capped by a pyramidal spire, at the top of which sits
        a golden weathervane in the form of the archangel Gabriel(the one in the nativity). The
        campanile reached its present form in 1514. The current tower was reconstructed in its
        present form in 1912 after the collapse of 1902.</string>
    <string name="st_marks_campanile_url">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/St_Mark%27s_Campanile</string>
    <string name="bridge_of_sighs_name">Bridge of Sighs</string>
    <string name="bridge_of_sighs_address">Piazza San Marco, 1, 30100\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="bridge_of_sighs_description">The Bridge of Sighs (Italian: Ponte dei Sospiri) is a
        bridge located in Venice, northern Italy. The enclosed bridge is made of white limestone,
        has windows with stone bars, and passes over the Rio di Palazzo and connects the New Prison
        (Prigioni Nuove) to the interrogation rooms in the Doge\'s Palace. It was designed by
        Antonio Contino (whose uncle Antonio da Ponte had designed the Rialto Bridge) and was built
        in 1600.\n\nThe view from the Bridge of Sighs was the last view of Venice that convicts saw
        before their imprisonment. The bridge\'s name, given by Lord Byron as a translation from the
        Italian "Ponte dei sospiri" in the 19th century, comes from the suggestion that prisoners
        would sigh at their final view of beautiful Venice through the window before being taken
        down to their cells. In reality, the days of inquisitions and summary executions were over
        by the time the bridge was built, and the cells under the palace roof were occupied mostly
        by small-time criminals. In addition, little could be seen from inside the bridge due to the
        stone grills covering the windows.</string>
    <string name="bridge_of_sighs_url">http://www.bridgeofsighs.info/</string>
    <string name="ca_rezzonico_name">Ca\' Rezzonico</string>
    <string name="ca_rezzonico_address">Dorsoduro, 3136, 30123\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="ca_rezzonico_description">Ca\' Rezzonico is a palazzo on the Grand Canal in the
        Dorsoduro sestiere of Venice, Italy. Today, it is a public museum dedicated to 18th-century
        Venice (Museo del Settecento Veneziano) and one of the 11 venues managed by the Fondazione
        Musei Civici di Venezia.</string>
    <string name="ca_rezzonico_url">http://carezzonico.visitmuve.it/en/home/</string>
    <string name="basilica_di_manta_maria_della_salute_name">
        Basilica di Santa Maria della Salute</string>
    <string name="basilica_di_manta_maria_della_salute_address">
        Fondamenta Salute, 30123\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="basilica_di_manta_maria_della_salute_description">Santa Maria della Salute
        (English: Saint Mary of Health), commonly known simply as the Salute, is a Roman Catholic
        church and minor basilica located at Punta della Dogana in the Dorsoduro sestiere of the city
        of Venice, Italy.\n\nIt stands on the narrow finger of Punta della Dogana, between the Grand
        Canal and the Giudecca Canal, at the Bacino di San Marco, making the church visible when
        entering the Piazza San Marco from the water. The Salute is part of the parish of the Gesuati
        and is the most recent of the so-called plague churches.\n\nIn 1630, Venice experienced an
        unusually devastating outbreak of the plague. As a votive offering for the city\'s
        deliverance from the pestilence, the Republic of Venice vowed to build and dedicate a church
        to Our Lady of Health (or of Deliverance, Italian: Salute). The church was designed in the
        then fashionable baroque style by Baldassare Longhena, who studied under the architect
        Vincenzo Scamozzi. Construction began in 1631. Most of the objects of art housed in the
        church bear references to the Black Death.\n\nThe dome of the Salute was an important
        addition to the Venice skyline and soon became emblematic of the city, inspiring artists like
        Canaletto, J. M. W. Turner, John Singer Sargent, and the Venetian artist Francesco Guardi.
    </string>
    <string name="basilica_di_manta_maria_della_salute_url">
        https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Santa_Maria_della_Salute</string>

    <!-- ATTRACTIONS CATEGORY -->

    <string name="gondola_ride_name">Gondola Ride</string>
    <string name="gondola_ride_address">Take a gondola ride in Venice.</string>
    <string name="gondola_ride_description"> There are two important rules to remember about gondola
        rides in Venice:\n\nIf the price bothers you, don\'t do it.\n\nIf the price doesn\'t
        bother you, make sure you understood the gondolier correctly.\n\nFact is, a gondola cruise
        in Venice is like traveling by hansom cab in New York\'s Central Park: It can be a delightful
        experience, but only if you\'re able to forget the price and focus on the ride.</string>
    <string name="gondola_ride_url">https://www.venice-gondola-rides.com/</string>
    <string name="venice_food_and_wine_name">Venice Food and Wine</string>
    <string name="venice_food_and_wine_address">Try local food and wine.</string>
    <string name="venice_food_and_wine_description">Don\'t spoil your visit to Venice by eating in
        over-priced tourist traps – follow the locals\' lead and graze on bar snacks in back-street
        osterie.\n\nSpain is known for its tapas, particularly in the Basque region where it is
        called Pintxos. You\’ve probably had Greek mezes while on holiday in Greece but did you know
        that Venice has it own tradition of small sharing plates?\n\nVenetian cicchetti, pronounced
        (chi-KET-tee) can be found across the city in small traditional wine bars called bacari.\n\n
        So what makes bacari popular with Venetians? For one, these bars have maintained their
        traditional spirit with customers mingling around the bar, chatting and expecting nothing but
        good company.\n\nJust don\’t mention the t-word (tapas) you don’t want to offend the locals.
        \n\nA cicchetti pub crawl is called giro d\'ombra. Giro means \'stroll\' and \'ombra\' slang
        for a glass of wine, means \'shade\'.\n\nIf you want an authentic experience of Venice, you
        need to be adventurous and go for a wander. Getting lost is probably the best way to do this.
        \n\nThe further you venture from St Mark\’s square, the more bacari you will stumble upon.
        Backstreet bacari\’s are where you find the locals – pop in for a glass of wine and some
        snacks.\n\nThe good thing about bacari is that usually won\’t be penalised for sitting down,
        although most people prefer to stand, but the if bar is big enough, there may be some table
        and chairs to rest weary feet.\n\nThese small hole-in-the-wall eateries have lots of tasty
        morsels for you to try.\n\nSome typical food you might see on offer – deep fried mozzarella,
        gorgonzola, calamari, and artichoke hearts – basically anything you can put on a toothpick.
    </string>
    <string name="venice_food_and_wine_url">https://www.venicebitesfoodtours.com/</string>
    <string name="the_carnival_of_venice_name">The Carnival of Venice</string>
    <string name="the_carnival_of_venice_address">
        The Carnival of Venice is an annual festival held in Venice.</string>
    <string name="the_carnival_of_venice_description"> During the Carnival (Carnevale), this most
        magical of cities fills with a mass of masked party-goers - posing and preening, dancing and
        philandering, in a slightly surreal re-invention of a great tradition of the city.\n\n
        Glancing at the portrayals of 18th-century Venetian life in the works of Pietro Longhi or
        Gabriele Bella in the Querini Stampalia gallery or the Ca\’ Rezzonico museum will reveal that
        was exactly what Venice in its party prime was all about. It\’s not for everybody. It can be
        intensely crowded, and rates in hotels and restaurants soar. But it is a unique occasion, and
        a great time to see the city in a new and exciting light. </string>
    <string name="the_carnival_of_venice_url">https://venice-carnival-italy.com/</string>
    <string name="campanile_view_name">Campanile View</string>
    <string name="campanile_view_address">
        Watch the whole city from the top of the Campanile.</string>
    <string name="campanile_view_description">A visit to the top of the Bell tower is obvious of
        course to be able to enjoy the superb view that it gives on all city of Venice,
        Giudecca and other closest islands such as San Giorgio, Murano and Lido.</string>
    <string name="campanile_view_url">http://www.basilicasanmarco.it/basilica/campanile/?lang=en</string>
    <string name="casanovas_story_name">Casanova\'s Story</string>
    <string name="casanovas_story_address">
        Follow famous lover\'s steps.</string>
    <string name="casanovas_story_description">Are you dreaming of retracing the history of famous
        Giacomo Casanova? Book now our unprecedented Casanova tour  in Venice, Italy: visit Casanova
        sites with a guide walking along his trails to discover the places that have seen the actions
        of the famous Venetian womanizer! A walk around Casanova\'s favorite city, where all the
        sites he frequented represent a kind of Casanova Venice museum.</string>
    <string name="casanovas_story_url">https://www.venetoinside.com/tours-activities-in-veneto/tour/
        venice-casanova-tour/</string>
    <string name="museo_della_musica_name">Museo della Musica</string>
    <string name="museo_della_musica_address">Visit the Museum of Music,
        it is different than all the others.</string>
    <string name="museo_della_musica_description">Housed in the restored neoclassical Chiesa di San
        Maurizio, this collection of rare 17th- to 20th-century instruments is accompanied by
        informative panels on the life and times of Venice\’s Antonio Vivaldi. To hear these
        instruments in action, check out the kiosk with CDs and concert tickets for Interpreti
        Veneziani, which runs the museum.</string>
    <string name="museo_della_musica_url">http://www.museodellamusica.com/en</string>
    <string name="the_peggy_guggenheim_collection_name">The Peggy Guggenheim Collection</string>
    <string name="the_peggy_guggenheim_collection_address">
        Visit the modern art museum on the Grand Canal in Venice.</string>
    <string name="the_peggy_guggenheim_collection_description">The Peggy Guggenheim Collection is a
        modern art museum on the Grand Canal in the Dorsoduro sestiere of Venice, Italy. It is one
        of the most visited attractions in Venice. The collection is housed in the Palazzo Venier
        dei Leoni, an 18th-century palace, which was the home of the American heiress Peggy
        Guggenheim for three decades. She began displaying her private collection of modern artworks
        to the public seasonally in 1951. After her death in 1979, it passed to the Solomon R.
        Guggenheim Foundation, which eventually opened the collection year-round.\n\nThe collection
        includes works of prominent Italian futurists and American modernists working in such genres
        as Cubism, Surrealism and Abstract expressionism. It also includes sculptural works.</string>
    <string name="the_peggy_guggenheim_collection_url">
        http://www.guggenheim-venice.it/default.html</string>
    <string name="lido_islands_beach_name">Lido Island\'s Beach</string>
    <string name="lido_islands_beach_address">Perfect retreat from crowded streets of Venice.</string>
    <string name="lido_islands_beach_description">The Lido, or Venice Lido (Lido di Venezia), is an
        11-kilometre (7-mile) long sandbar in Venice, northern Italy; it is home to about 20,000
        residents. The Venice Film Festival takes place at the Lido every September.\n\nThe island
        is home to three settlements. The Lido itself, in the north, is home to the Film Festival,
        the Grand Hotel des Bains, the Venice Casino and the Grand Hotel Excelsior. Malamocco, in
        the centre, was the first and, for a long time, the only settlement. It was at one time home
        to the Doge of Venice. Alberoni at the southern end is home to the golf course. Frequent
        public buses run the length of the island along the main street.\n\nAt least half the
        Adriatic side of the island is a sandy beach, much of it belonging to the various hotels that
        house the summer tourists. These include the renowned Excelsior and the Des Bains, setting
        for Thomas Mann\'s classic novel Death in Venice, currently undergoing major renovation.
        These beaches are private, though towards the northern and southern ends of the island there
        are two enormous public beaches. The Adriatic Sea is fairly clean and warm, ideal for
        children, with only the occasional jellyfish to disturb swimming.\n\nThe heart of the island
        is the Gran Viale Santa Maria Elisabetta, a wide street approximately 700 m long that leads
        from the lagoon and vaporetto (water bus) stop on one side across to the sea on the other.
        It houses hotels, shops, and tourist-centric restaurants.\n\nVenezia Lido, a public airport
        suitable for smaller aircraft, is found on the NE end of Lido di Venezia. It has a 1000m
        grass runway.</string>
    <string name="lido_islands_beach_url">http://www.lidodivenezia.it/</string>
    <string name="murano_name">Murano - The Glass Island</string>
    <string name="murano_address">Murano is really well known for the glass making.</string>
    <string name="murano_description">Murano is an island town close to Venice\'s northern shore.
        It\'s not as large or as important as its neighbour, but it does still have a Grand Canal,
        some elegant palazzi and a couple of fine churches. Murano is most famous for its glassmaking
        factories, and tourists throng the main canalsides, which are lined with shops and showrooms.
        In 1291 Venice\'s glass furnaces were all moved to this island, to protect the city from
        outbreaks of fire. Venice was famed for its glass, and any glass-makers who left the lagoon
        were viewed as traitors - there are lurid tales of them being pursued and assassinated. Glass
        is still Murano\'s trade, although it\'s as much a tourist attraction as a centre of industry
        nowadays, and lots of the glass on sale comes from China. You\'ll see glass everywhere you
        turn: an outdoors Christmas tree of glass; a street-shrine with a glass Madonna and Child.
        It\'s a good place to buy your gifts, and although the canalsides get crowded, there are so
        many shops that you can generally manage to browse in peace.</string>
    <string name="murano_url">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Murano</string>
    <string name="colorful_burano_island_name">Colorful Burano Island</string>
    <string name="colorful_burano_island_address">
        Burano is famous for its colorful houses and lace making.</string>
    <string name="colorful_burano_island_description">All visitors of Burano remain intrigued by the
        many colours and the colorful houses that are reflected into the green waters of channels,
        by the leaning bell tower, by the tranquility and the calmness with which the elderly ladies
        embroider original Burano lace by their tombolo (or lace pillow), while they are laughing and
        chatting in squares among them. It seems to be in paradise. Children who dart freely with
        their bicycles, balconies with multicolored flowers, fishermen who put up fresh fish from
        their traditional boats.</string>
    <string name="colorful_burano_island_url">http://www.isoladiburano.it/en/</string>

    <!-- HOTELS CATEGORY -->

    <string name="hilton_molino_stucky_name">Hilton Molino Stucky Venice</string>
    <string name="hilton_molino_stucky_address">Giudecca, 810, 30133\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="hilton_molino_stucky_description">This luxurious hotel in a restored, redbrick
        flour mill on Giudecca Island, is a 6-minute walk from the nearest vaporetto stop and a
        12-minute walk from the Peggy Guggenheim Collection. It\'s 2.5 km from Rialto Bridge.\n\n
        Sophisticated rooms feature Wi-Fi (fee) and flat-screen TVs; some have Venice views.
        Upgraded options offer access to an executive lounge; suites add living rooms,
        marble bathrooms and dining rooms. Room service is available.\n\n
        Breakfast (fee) is offered in 1 of 4 restaurants. There\'s also a swanky rooftop bar and
        a relaxed lounge. Other amenities include a rooftop pool (seasonal), a spa and a gym. An
        area shuttle boat is available.</string>
    <string name="hilton_molino_stucky_url">http://www3.hilton.com/en/hotels/italy/hilton-molino-
        stucky-venice-VCEHIHI/index.html?WT.mc_id=zELWAKN0EMEA1HI2DMH3LocalSearch4DGGenericx6VCEHIHI
    </string>
    <string name="starhotels_splendid_name">Starhotels Splendid Venice</string>
    <string name="starhotels_splendid_address">San Marco Mercerie, 760, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="starhotels_splendid_description">This high-end canal-side hotel is 0.3 km from
        Saint Mark\'s Basilica.\n\nCozy, elegant rooms with wood floors feature free Wi-Fi,
        flat-screen TVs, minifridges and marble bathrooms. Regal suites add living areas and
        complimentary wine, and some have canal views. Upgraded suites offer butler service,
        iPod/iPhone docks, espresso machines, and whirlpool tubs, and some have private terraces.
        Room service is available 24/7.\n\nBreakfast is complimentary. Amenities include a posh
        restaurant with a glass ceiling and a fireplace, plus a stylish canal-view bar. There\'s
        also a rooftop terrace, a library and water taxi access. Pets may be welcome with prior notice.
    </string>
    <string name="starhotels_splendid_url">https://www.starhotels.com/en/our-hotels/splendid-venice-
        venice/?utm_source=google&amp;utm_medium=local&amp;utm_campaign=glocal</string>
    <string name="jw_marriott_venice_resort_spa_name">JW Marriott Venice Resort &#038; Spa</string>
    <string name="jw_marriott_venice_resort_spa_address">
        Isola delle Rose, Laguna di San\u00A0Marco, 30133\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="jw_marriott_venice_resort_spa_description">Set on a private island in the Venetian
        lagoon, this palatial resort is a 13-minute boat shuttle from Piazza San Marco and a
        9-minute boat shuttle from the Bridge of Sighs.\n\nChic rooms feature Wi-Fi (fee),
        flat-screen TVs, and tea and coffeemaking facilities. Suites add sitting areas. Upgraded
        quarters offer balconies; some have separate bedrooms, free Wi-Fi and 2nd levels. A 2-bedroom
        villa with a pool is available.\n\nA boat shuttle and breakfast are complimentary. There are
        also 4 restaurants and 2 bars, plus a spa, an outdoor pool and a hot tub. Pets are welcome.
    </string>
    <string name="jw_marriott_venice_resort_spa_url">http://www.marriott.com/hotels/travel/vcejw-jw-
        marriott-venice-resort-and-spa/</string>
    <string name="hotel_nh_collection_venezia_palazzo_barocci_name">
        Hotel NH Collection Venezia Palazzo Barocci</string>
    <string name="hotel_nh_collection_venezia_palazzo_barocci_address">
        Corte dell\'Albero, 3878/a, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_nh_collection_venezia_palazzo_barocci_description">Set on the Grand Canal,
        this elegant hotel in an 1890s-era former palace is a 10-minute walk from Piazza San Marco
        and 14 minutes\' walk from the Bridge of Sighs.\n\nUpscale rooms have free Wi-Fi, flat-screen
        TVs, minibars, and tea and coffeemaking facilities. Upgraded rooms add canal views. Suites
        offer separate living areas; some have private terraces.\n\nThe hotel provides complimentary
        buffet breakfast. Additional amenities include a refined lounge bar, a garden area and a
        private dock, as well as a business center and meeting space. An airport shuttle (by boat)
        is available for a fee.</string>
    <string name="hotel_nh_collection_venezia_palazzo_barocci_url">https://www.nh-collection.com/it/
        hotel/nh-collection-venezia-palazzo-barocci</string>
    <string name="hotel_a_la_commedia_name">Hotel A La Commedia</string>
    <string name="hotel_a_la_commedia_address">San Marco, 4596/A, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_a_la_commedia_description">This elegant hotel is 2 minutes\' walk from Rialto
        (Riva del Carbon) ferry stop, 5 minutes\' walk from Piazza San Marco and 6 minutes\' walk from
        Saint Mark\'s Basilica.\n\nThe opulent rooms come with complimentary Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs
        and minibars, as well as iPod docks, safes and windows that open. They also have marble
        bathrooms. Suites have pull-out couches and seating areas. Room service is available.\n\n
        The hotel serves complimentary breakfast in a simple but stylish restaurant. There is also a
        trendy cocktail bar and a business center. Parking is available for a fee.</string>
    <string name="hotel_a_la_commedia_url">http://www.commediahotel.com/</string>
    <string name="hotel_danieli_name">Hotel Danieli</string>
    <string name="hotel_danieli_address">Castello, 4196, 30122\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_danieli_description">Set in a lavish Venetian building, this luxurious
        waterfront hotel is a 5-minute walk from Piazza San Marco and 1.3 km from the iconic Grand
        Canal.\n\nFeaturing high ceilings and plush drapes, the opulent rooms offer free Wi-Fi and
        flat-screen TVs. Upgraded rooms add features such as tapestries and sitting areas, while
        suites offer lagoon views. Room service is available.\n\nThe refined restaurant serves
        gourmet Venetian cuisine. There\'s also a cocktail bar, a wine suite, a terrace with lagoon
        views, and a fitness room. In-room massages are also available.</string>
    <string name="hotel_danieli_url">http://www.danielihotelvenice.com/</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_name">Hotel Metropole</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_address">Riva degli Schiavoni, 4149, 30122\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_description">This upscale hotel is an 8-minute walk from Saint
        Mark\'s Basilica, a 9-minute walk from Piazza San Marco and 1.5 km from the Grand Canal.\n\n
        Ornate rooms and suites with plush decor and elegant furniture come with seating areas;
        1 suite has a rooftop terrace.\n\n</string>
    <string name="hotel_metropole_url">http://www.hotelmetropole.com/</string>
    <string name="belmond_hotel_cipriani_name">Belmond Hotel Cipriani</string>
    <string name="belmond_hotel_cipriani_address">Giudecca, 10, 30133\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="belmond_hotel_cipriani_description">A 15-minute stroll from Piazza San Marco,
        this lavish, landmark hotel is also 13 minutes by foot from St. Mark\'s Basilica.\n\nElegant
        rooms with garden or lagoon views, offer flat-screens and free Wi-Fi, plus iPod docks and
        minibars; some have balconies or kitchenettes. Suites add plush seating areas or lounges, and
        hints including poolside views, antique artworks or terraces with hot tubs. Room service is
        available.\n\nFree perks include breakfast and a local area shuttle boat. There\'s also a
        refined restaurant, a waterfront bistro and a chic bar, in addition to an Olympic-sized
        outdoor pool, a spa and tennis courts. Closed November to March.</string>
    <string name="belmond_hotel_cipriani_url">https://www.belmond.com/hotel-cipriani-venice/</string>
    <string name="boscolo_venezia_name">Boscolo Venezia</string>
    <string name="boscolo_venezia_address">
        Fondamenta Madonna dell\'Orto, 3500, 30121\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="boscolo_venezia_description">Set 1.8 km from the Grand Canal, this ornate hotel is
        also 1.9 km from Saint Mark\'s Basilica.\n\nDecorated with antique furnishings, the refined,
        period-style rooms and suites also have free Wi-Fi and cable TVs. Suites add living areas,
        and luxe upgraded suites have whirlpool tubs in en suite bathrooms.\n\nThere\'s free motorboat
        shuttle service to St. Mark Square. The hotel has a restaurant for Venetian and international
        cuisine, plus an elegant bar. Other amenities include a high-end spa, a garden, and meeting
        and event facilities.</string>
    <string name="boscolo_venezia_url">http://venezia.boscolohotels.com/</string>
    <string name="canal_grande_hotel_name">Canal Grande Hotel</string>
    <string name="canal_grande_hotel_address">
        Santa Croce, 932, 30135 Campo San Simeone Grande, Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="canal_grande_hotel_description">Overlooking the Canal Grande, this ornate hotel is
        a 5-minute walk from Stazione di Venezia Santa Lucia and 1.9 km from the Piazza San Marco.\n\n
        The refined rooms are inspired by Venetian art and history with gold-framed mirrors, Murano
        glass, briar-root furniture decorated with gold leaf, and soft wood floors. All have en suite
        marble bathrooms, free Wi-Fi, flat-screen TVs and air-conditioning. Suites add separate living
        areas.\n\nAmenities include a free breakfast buffet, a waterside terrace and a bar with velvet
        armchairs. The Rococo-style lobby has a rose marble fireplace. The hotel is accessed directly
        from the canal, as well as from dry land.</string>
    <string name="canal_grande_hotel_url">http://www.hotelcanalgrande.it/</string>

    <!-- RESTAURANTS CATEGORY -->
    <string name="il_paradiso_perduto_name">Il Paradiso Perduto</string>
    <string name="il_paradiso_perduto_address">Fondamenta Misericordia, 2540, 30100 Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="il_paradiso_perduto_description">Fondamenta della Misericordia is the place to be.
        In this walk that runs from Venice Ghetto to Strada Nova, you can find some of the most
        interesting spots for young people (and not only) in Venice.\n\nIndeed the most famous is
        Paradiso Perduto. What about this legendary place? It was born in the 80s out of desire by a
        group of students, including Maurizio Adamo who is still the manager. Within some years
        Paradiso has became a reference point for those interested in listening to jazz music and of
        course in tasting a good Venetian meal.\n\nThe restaurant is a typical Osteria, always
        chaotic and overcrowded but with a unique atmosphere. Adamo runs between wooden tables
        offering wine from the carafe with a good smile.This place is perfect for a Sunday lunch
        outside in Fondamenta or for a dinner with friends.\n\nCheck out the weekly calendar for
        events and book in advance. On Saturday, even if you have a reservation, you will probably
        have to wait for your table.</string>
    <string name="il_paradiso_perduto_url">https://ilparadisoperduto.wordpress.com/</string>
    <string name="osteria_enoteca_ai_artisti_name">Osteria Enoteca Ai Artisti</string>
    <string name="osteria_enoteca_ai_artisti_address">
        Fondamenta della Toletta 1169\abc, 30123\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="osteria_enoteca_ai_artisti_description">Good things come in small packages at this
        Dorsoduro osteria, which manages to turn out gourmet lunches and dinners in a space that
        would be tight even for a neighbourhood bar. It can seat just 20 – including two perched at
        the window shelf – but it\'s worth the claustrophobia, as the food here is seriously good.
        They pride themselves on having no freezer: the militantly fresh and local menu changes
        every day, according to what the market provides. Nothing fancy: just the kind of excellent
        home cooking that so many chefs strive to reproduce.</string>
    <string name="osteria_enoteca_ai_artisti_url">http://www.enotecaartisti.com/</string>
    <string name="bistrot_de_venise_name">Bistrot de Venise</string>
    <string name="bistrot_de_venise_address">
        Calle dei Fabbri, Sestiere San Marco, 4685, 30124\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="bistrot_de_venise_description">Bistrot de Venise first opened in 1993 and has since
        become a hangout and meeting place where the figurative arts, poetry and culture combine,
        simply, with Food and Wine....1999 saw the start of our research into Rare Wines and
        Historical Venetian Cuisine, strengthening our concept of applying culture to local and
        regional Gastronomy and Wine. ...our hard work still continues today... Gastronomy &amp;
        Wine…extensive research on the history of venetian Cuisine and Wines, from its noble origins
        to the present time. The Historic &amp; Renaissance Venetian Cuisine revised and suggested
        by our Chef Mario Missese and his young team. Our House, unique in town, offer a gastronomic
        trip back to the past glories of Venice following its history &amp; tradition. ”Award winning”
        wine list, for the quality and variety of the selected rare wines from the Veneto Region and
        the North-East of Italy. Professional wine tasting (free) all year round.
        "..exciting Wine List" .. (see Michelin Guide 2012) specialized in the research of many Rare
        Wines, a truly unique selection purchased directly from small producers with the help of
        Istituto Sperimentale di Viticoltura di Conegliano. More than 60 options by the glass and a
        wide selection of the most prestigious italian vineyards. Prized Wine List by Italian
        Sommelier Association for best 15 in the Veneto Region at Vinitaly 2010.</string>
    <string name="bistrot_de_venise_url">http://www.bistrotdevenise.com/?lang=en</string>
    <string name="restaurant_la_caravella_name">Restaurant La Caravella</string>
    <string name="restaurant_la_caravella_address">
        Calle Larga XXII Marzo, 2399, 30100 San Marco, Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="restaurant_la_caravella_description">La Caravella restaurant in Venice can be
        discovered immediately behind the newly-restored La Fenice theatre, just a few paces from the
        Piazza San Marco. Stepping inside, you will feel as if you have entered an antique sailing
        ship, with dark wood paneling, capstans and ropes and leaded windows. In summer, you may not
        step inside at all as La Caravella moves into a flower-filled courtyard complete with
        original wells, or the lighter courtyard dining room with typical Venetian ambience. The menu
        is typically Venetian too, with dishes like classic saor, marinated sardines with onions,
        pine kernels and raisins, fish soup, or oven orast turbot with potatoes and olives. In
        addition, the chef uses fresh seasonal ingredients to create trendier fare. The excellent
        wine list features both historical wine producers and smaller boutique vintners. Planning a
        party? La Caravella welcomes wedding receptions, private dinners, banquets, corporate
        entertaining, even coffee breaks. The garden seats up to 65 and one of the dining rooms up
        to 75.</string>
    <string name="restaurant_la_caravella_url">http://www.restaurantlacaravella.com/</string>
    <string name="osteria_antico_giardinetto_name">Osteria Antico Giardinetto</string>
    <string name="osteria_antico_giardinetto_address">
        Calle dei Morti, 2253, 30135\u00A0Santa\u00A0Croce, Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="osteria_antico_giardinetto_description">The name refers to the intimate garden
        where co-owner Larisa will welcome you warmly, once you\'ve wound your way from the Rialto or
        San Stae down the narrow calle to this romantic locale. (There\'s an indoor dining room as
        well, but the garden is covered and heated in winter.) Larisa\'s husband, Virgilio, mans the
        kitchen, where he prepares such dishes as sea bass in salt crust and a grilled fish platter.
        Be sure to try the homemade gnocchi or pasta—perhaps the tagliolini (thin spaghetti) with
        scallops and artichokes. You\'ll also find some fine meat options here. Desserts, like the
        chocolate mousse or crème caramel, are homemade as well. The wine list features some
        excellent regional selections.</string>
    <string name="osteria_antico_giardinetto_url">http://www.anticogiardinetto.it/</string>
    <string name="ai_mercanti_name">Ai Mercanti</string>
    <string name="ai_mercanti_address">Calle Fuseri, 4346/a, 30011\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="ai_mercanti_description">Ristorante Ai Mercanti in the heart of Venice between the
        Rialto Bridge and Piazza San Marco is an upmarket, romantic restaurant in very cool style
        that enjoys a high-flying gastronomic reputation. The vaulted dining room is decorated in
        sophisticated terracotta and black with impressive shining globe lighting. The bar is wittily
        decorated with dressmakers’ forms and sexy corsets – great conversation starters. The menu is
        classically-inspired Venetian of a high order, focusing on things from the sea and changing
        every two months to take advantage of the and array of the freshest ingredients
        in true Italian style and pastas and desserts are all made in-house. In warm weather the
        dining room sprawls out onto the adjoining campiello for the loveliest al fresco dining
        anywhere – the Venetians who crowd Ai Mercanti certainly think so. </string>
    <string name="ai_mercanti_url">http://www.aimercanti.com/comearrivare.htm</string>
    <string name="la_zucca_name">La Zucca</string>
    <string name="la_zucca_address">Santa Croce 1762, 30135\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="la_zucca_description">The simple place settings, lattice-wood walls, and mélange
        of languages make La Zucca (the pumpkin) feel much like a typical, somewhat sophisticated
        vegetarian restaurant that you could find in any European city. What makes La Zucca special
        is the use of fresh, local ingredients (many of which, like the particularly sweet zucca
        itself, aren\'t normally found outside northern Italy), and simply great cooking. Though
        the menu does have superb meat dishes such as the piccata di pollo ai caperi e limone
        con riso (sliced chicken with capers and lemon served with rice), more attention is paid to
        dishes from the garden: try the radicchio di Treviso con funghi e scaglie di Montasio
        (with mushrooms and shavings of Montasio cheese), the finocchi piccanti con olive
        (fennel in a spicy tomato-olive sauce), or the house\'s signature dish—the flan di zucca,
        a luscious, naturally sweet, pumpkin pudding topped with slivered, aged ricotta cheese.</string>
    <string name="la_zucca_url">http://www.lazucca.it/en</string>
    <string name="osteria_alla_ciurma_name">Osteria Alla Ciurma</string>
    <string name="osteria_alla_ciurma_address">Calle Galeazza, 406/A, 30125\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="osteria_alla_ciurma_description">The morning Rialto market is the liveliest part of
        the Serenissima, where locals come to do their food shopping and stop off for a drink and
        bite at one of the bars in the maze of side streets. The insider address to track down is
        Alla Ciurma, an ancient storeroom converted into a tiny bar resembling the inside of a boat,
        hence the name, The Crew. Working in a miniscule kitchen, owner Marco Paola makes creamy
        baccalà mantecato (creamy codfish mousse) tuna polpette, or “meatballs”, and courgette
        flowers stuffed with mozzarella and anchovies. Now he is experimenting by marinating raw fish
        in fruity olive oil and herbs – monkfish with olives and mint, seabream with basil and lemon,
        mackerel with laurel leaves and onion. The excellent house wine is 90 cents a glass,
        cicheti are €1-€1.50, with a sharing plate of cheeses and salami at €15.</string>
    <string name="osteria_alla_ciurma_url">http://www.osteriaciurma.it/</string>
    <string name="la_colombina_name">La Colombina</string>
    <string name="la_colombina_address">Cannaregio, 1828, 30131\u00A0Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="la_colombina_description">Right in the heart of Venice, between Santa Lucia train
        station and the Rialto Bridge, and just a few steps away from the Casino, you will find a
        restaurant where we have translated our welcoming philosophy into a concrete culinary
        experience: "La Colombina".\n\nThere are numberless reasons to visit and revisit Venice, but
        now you can add one more: "La Colombina", a gastronomic experience inspired by tradition but
        also focused on contemporaneity. In short, a new "classic" ranging from traditional Venetian
        dishes to unique gourmet temptations going from aperitifs to lunches and special occasions.
    </string>
    <string name="la_colombina_url">http://www.ristorantelacolombina.eu/it/</string>
    <string name="corte_sconta_name">Corte Sconta</string>
    <string name="corte_sconta_address">Calle del Pestrin, 3886, 30122 Castello, Venice, Italy</string>
    <string name="corte_sconta_description">The restaurant Calle Sconta is located on  Court of
        Pestrin, Castello 3886, and is a landmark restaurant in the Venetian. The quality and
        freshness of the season followed by the service in a courteous and attentive. Strengths of
        the menu are clams with ginger, the crab in water, creamed cod, sardines in sauce, and the
        inevitable fresh pasta homemade daily and combined with seafood and vegetables. Weekly rest
        on Sundays and Mondays.</string>
    <string name="corte_sconta_url">http://www.cortescontavenezia.com/</string>

    <!-- DESCRIPTION ACTIVITY -->
    <string name="description_more_info">more info</string>

</resources>